Now that the eyes and skin are done, the finishing touch is the lips.
I'm going to use one of the pink powders, which was the same kind of mauve color I used on her lid.
I'm going to mix that with a clear lip gloss, and we're going to use that as lip gloss or lipstick.
Again, you can use the back of your hand.
You can use a Petri dish, a plate, anything just to mix it.
You just want to take a little bit of powder at a time and mix it with the clear gloss until you get your desired color.
This is a natural look, so I don't want it too pinky.
I just want it really natural.
I'm going to add a little more lip gloss.
You can use lip liner if you want also.
That's completely up to you.
For her, she's got nice big plump lips, so I'm just going to do the lip gloss without the lip liner.
Look how pretty that is.
Very, very neutral.
Take any of these powders.
This would be good a blush too, a really sheer pink blush.
If you have a pink gloss you love, but you just want to add some oomph to it, you don't have to use a clear.
You can use any color.
If you have a nude lip gloss that you want a little more pink, this is the time where you can experiment and mix and match.
I just want it a little more glossy, so I'm going to add a little more gloss.
I really used very little powder.
Just enough to give a bit of a color.
Look how pretty that is.
We just invented a new lip gloss.